jakprints.com 2011-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Jakprints, Inc

Products Services Create Designers Support My Account

## Products

Choose from a full range of full color offset, digital screen printed and embroidered products to bring your brand or message to life.

### View all:

  * Full Color Products
  * Apparel Products
  * Sticker Products
  * Wide Format Products

### Need something custom?

Request a Quote

### Identity

  * Business Cards
  * Favicards
  * Brochures - One Fold
  * Brochures - Tri-Fold
  * Letterhead
  * Envelopes
  * Mailing Labels
  * Pocket Folders

### Promotions

  * Post Cards
  * Folding Cards
  * Flyers
  * One Sheets
  * Posters
  * Door Hangers
  * Rack Cards
  * Rip Cards
  * Banners

### Media

  * CD Insert/Tray Cards
  * CD Wallets
  * CD/Mix Tapes
  * Single CD O-Cards
  * CD Booklets
  * DVD Covers
  * DVD Inserts
  * Record Flats
  * Record Jackets

### Events

  * Table Tents
  * VIP Passes
  * Tickets
  * Tote Bags
  * Banners

### Multi-Page

  * Catalogs
  * Comic Books
  * Magazines
  * Calendars
  * Note Pads

### Stickers & Labels

  * Roll Stickers
  * Magnets
  * Bumper Stickers
  * Window Decals
  * Mailing Labels

### T-Shirts

  * Crew Neck
  * V-Neck
  * Ringers
  * Raglans
  * Long Sleeve Ts
  * All-Over Printing

### Women's

  * Baby Dolls
  * Spaghetti Straps
  * Tank Tops
  * Underwear

### Shirts

  * Polos
  * Workshirts
  * All-Over Printing

### Outerwear

  * Sweatshirts
  * Hoodies
  * Zip Hoodies
  * Zip Joggers

### Headwear

  * Long Beanies
  * Short Beanies
  * Ball Cap
  * Fatigue Hat

### Bags

  * Messenger Bags
  * Tote Bags

## Services

High-end printing and product development services along with the right people to make it all happen.

### Ready to start?

Create your own and get a quote.

### Or view our Products:

  * Full Color Products
  * Apparel Products
  * Sticker Products
  * Wide Format Products

### Offset Printing

  * Matte Coatings
  * Custom Spot Coatings
  * Paper Stocks
  * Custom Pantone Inks

### Screen Printing

  * Inks
  * Effects
  * Apparel Stocks
  * Custom Print Locations

### Sticker Printing

  * Flexo Stickers
  * Screen Printed
  * Short Run Stickers
  * Sticker Inks
  * Sticker Stocks

### Embroidery

  * Digitization & Embroidery
  * Custom Embroidery Effects
  * Specialty Threads
  * Apparel Stocks

### Fulfillment

  * Full Service Shipping
  * Multiple Locations
  * Pick Ups
  * Direct Mail Service
  * Slip Sheet Inserts

### Finishing Options

  * Laminating
  * Binding
  * Ticket Numbering
  * Variable Data
  * Perforation
  * Scoring
  * Folding
  * Drilling
  * Rounded Corners
  * Embossing
  * Foil Stamping
  * Die Cutting
  * Manual Assembly
  * Shrink Wrapping

### Pre-Press Services

  * Standard File Prep
  * Hard-copy Proof
  * Digital Proofing

### Wide Format Printing

  * Stocks and Applications
  * Photo Paper
  * Additional Options
  * Double-Sided Tape
  * Foam Core Mounting

### Retail Ready Packaging

  * Folding and Polybagging
  * Custom Labels
  * Relabeling and De-labeling
  * Custom Hang Tags
  * Shrink Wrap

## Create Yours

Designers, clients and Jakprints staff collaborate on custom products.

### Create Custom Products & Request Quotes

#### Full Color Products

Choose from the full range of paper stocks and finishing options to create your own full color printed materials or products.

Custom Order | Custom Quote

#### Sticker Products

Create custom sticker products using the full range of stocks, shapes and colors.

Custom Order | Custom Quote

#### Wide Format Products

Create Banners, Over size posters and Art Prints in any size across many different canvas, paper and vinyl stocks.

Custom Order | Custom Quote

#### Screen Printed Apparel

Full range apparel styles with high-end effects and durable traditional ink.

Custom Order | Custom Quote

#### All-Over Printed Apparel

Create full front and back T-Shirts in quantities of one or many.

#### Embroidered Apparel

Create high end embroidered apparel across many stocks using many effects and threads.

Custom Order | Custom Quote

## Designers

Need graphic design, illustration or merch design? Find the right designer for your next project. 

### Find Designers

Find the right partner for your next design job.

View All Designers

## Support

Get help with common and specific product and printing related questions from the pros.

### Help & Reference

  * File Prep Guides
  * Templates
  * FAQs

## My Account

Track order status, manage payment and fulfillment details for your jobs.

### Account

  * View My Account
  * My Order History
  * My Quote History
  * My Billing Information

### Preferences

  * Shipping Preferences
  * Shipping Addresses
  * Change My Email Address
  * Change My Password

### Can't log into your account? 

  * Reset your Password

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Jakprints collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Jakprints's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Jakprints's visitors use its website.

Jakprints also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Jakprints does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Jakprints's websites choose to interact with Jakprints in ways that require Jakprints to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Jakprints gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Jakprints are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. Jakprints does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Jakprints discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Jakprints's behalf or to provide services available at Jakprints's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Jakprints's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Jakprints will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Jakprints discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Jakprints believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Jakprints, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Jakprints website and have supplied your email address, Jakprints may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Jakprints and our products. We primarily use blogs and social media to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Jakprints takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Jakprints uses cookies to help Jakprints identify and track visitors, their usage of Jakprints website, and their website access preferences. Jakprints visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Jakprints's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Jakprints's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Jakprints may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Jakprints's sole discretion. Jakprints encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Thanks to [Automattic](http://automattic.com/) for its Creative Commons Sharealike-licensed privacy policy.
